

KOTLIAR **DMYTRO**Web developer

- Ukraine, Mykolaiv DC
- yardnight@gmail.com
- **3** +38(093)548-41-18

SOCIAL

- in @dmytro-kotliar
- 🚹 @dmytro.kotliar
- @vieweek
- @yardnight

PROFILE

I am Fornt-End developer and keen of UI/UX design. PhD graduated in Applied Geometry & Engineering Graphics. Before I was involved into different kind of engineering projects. I have startup founder experience. University part-time associated professor.

EDUCATION

- DOCTOR of PHILOSOPHY
 Applied Geometry And
 Engineering Graphics
 2009-2015
- MASTER of SCIENCE in ENERGY
 Admiral Makarov National

University of Shipbuilding 2007-2009

2007-2009

 BACHELOR of SCIENCE in MECHANICAL ENGINEERING Admiral Makarov National University of Shipbuilding 2003-2007

SKILLS

UMTH

Sass SASS

G CSS

🦸 GULP

JavaScript

- Git
- VS code
- IconFonts
- SVG
- Figma
- CorelDraw
- 3ds Max

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

June 2021 - Up to now | Freelance

You can find my projects on GITHUB: https://github.com/yardnight

MECHANICAL ENGINEER

March 2019 - March 2021 | C-Job Mykolaiv

Design engineering stage of routing for yacht systems as per diagram Pipe systems trace routing of supplier/consumer connection for ship equipment HVAC routing. Correction of yacht system diagram. Adjusting skeleton model, modeling production door arrangement. Production Documentation: cut part list drafting, construction and assembly drafting, hoisting plan and dim drafting. Hydraulic schemes production. Spear part list creation. Model developing of exterior outfit welding constructions for cutterladder arrangement. Drafting of production documentation.

CHIEF TECHNICAL OFFICER

July 2015 - January 2019 | MUTANT LLC

Invent modeling, patents providing. Production organization. Flow and structural simulation analysis. Team building. Coding manufacturer technological operation for CNC machine. Coding of post-processors for CNC machines (NCT, Siemence Sinumeric). Production control and optimization. Prototype research testing.

ASSOSIATE PROFESSOR

September 2009 - Up to now | Admiral Makarov National University of Shipbuilding

Reserching&Development. Deliver lectures. Organization of learning process. Test students. Write learning sources.

CERTIFICATES

Diploma of candidate of science | Ministry of Education and Science of Ukraine (2015)

Comparable to the Academic Degree of Doctor of Philosophy. Defined a thesis on speciality "Applied Geometry, Engineering Graphics".

Thank-you letter | Mykolaiv Municipal Council (2016)

For achievements in scientific work and on the occasion of the Day of Science.

Thank-you letter | Mykolaiv Regional Council (2020)

For a significant personal contribution to the development of national education, high professionalism in training, active life position on the occasion of Independence Day.

REFERENCES

Lead developer

Mr. Serhii Ustenko

Phone: +38(063)479-90-61 Email: ustenko.s.a.@gmail.com

Chief of FEM Department in C-Job Mykolaiv

Mr. Dmytro Volik

Phone: +38(093)108-10-17 Email: dmitriy.volik@gmail.com

Prorector of NUOS

Mr. Serhiy Slobodian

Phone: +38(067)722-47-76 Email: slo71nuos@gmail.com

MUTANT LLC Director

Mr. Alex Knizhnik

Phone: +38(093)969-24-79 Email: alex.knizhnik@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

- English (Intermidiate)
- Ukrainian (Native speaker)
- Russian (Native)

INTERESTS











